{
    "subject": "resource/PrepMe",
    "predicate": "ontology/industry",
    "object": "resource/Internet",
    "human_readable": "PrepMe operates in the Internet industry.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9143509864807129,
            "question": "What industry does PrepMe operate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8396056294441223,
            "question": "What are some of the emerging trends within the Internet industry that PrepMe might be involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8147909641265869,
            "question": "Are there any challenges faced by companies like PrepMe in the Internet industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7880166172981262,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a company that operates in the same industry as PrepMe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7787804007530212,
            "question": "Is PrepMe involved in the technology sector?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6928746104240417,
            "question": "What type of services might PrepMe offer based on its industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5256936550140381,
            "question": "How does PrepMe's work contribute to the broader Internet ecosystem?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5255455374717712,
            "question": "What is the future outlook for companies operating in the Internet industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3516204059123993,
            "question": "What are some of the major players in the Internet industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32947251200675964,
            "question": "How has the Internet industry changed over time?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=PrepMe operates in the Internet industry.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6048_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the major players in the Internet industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6048_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the future outlook for companies operating in the Internet industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6048_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does PrepMe's work contribute to the broader Internet ecosystem?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6048_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6048_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6048_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6048_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6048_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6048_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6048_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6048_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6048_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6048_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6048_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents clearly state that PrepMe uses web 2.0 technology and offers online test preparation services.  This strongly indicates operation within the internet industry.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about PrepMe, an online test preparation company based in Chicago, IL. They mention that PrepMe offers its services online and has partnered with brick-and-mortar companies to provide comprehensive test-preparation services, which supports the statement that PrepMe operates in the Internet industry."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}